National Coat & Suit Industry Recovery Board Records 5915
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Coat & Suit Industry Recovery Board Records
1932-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
National Coat & Suit Industry Recovery Board
5915
11 cubic feet
11 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5734520
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 17, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6036/010: National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Records 6167 mf: NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents on Microfilm 6168 mf: NYU Tamiment Library Collection of National Coat and Suit Recovery Board Documents (copy 2) on Microfilm 6245: National Recovery Administration National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board Statistical Data
National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board (U.S.)
5734520
- Amendment to Coat and Suit Code, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Amendment to Code, Textile Division (Washington), 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- American Arbitration Association, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Apparel Section, Deputy Administrator Correction Regarding Interpretation of Code, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Administrative Orders, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Appeals: Industrial Appeals Board, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Application to Code Authority, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Attorney General, State of New York Correction Regarding Case in Violation of Schanno Act, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Baltimore Office, Records, Correspondence (Jonas H. Glass), 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bank Resolutions and Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Better Business Bureau, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Blouse and Skirt Code Authority, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Boston: Wholesale Garment Association, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Boston Office: Correspondence. S.C. Hamburger, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Budget NRA, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Scope and Contents
  January 1935-June 1935
- Budget Resolutions, also included Payroll Resolutions, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- By Laws of Various Associations, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Chicago Office Records: S.J. Kanton, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  October 1933-May 1934
- Chicago Office Records: S.J. Kanton, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  June-December 1934
- Chicago Professional Correspondence (S.J. Kanton, Doctor Arthur Rubin), 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Cleveland Office: Records/Correspondence Frank A. Garvey, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  October 1933-July 1934
- Cleveland Office: Records/Correspondence, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  August 1934-December 1935
- Code Authority Meetings (Minutes-Forms: Compliance, Violation, Label Sales, Investigations), 1933 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Coat and Suit Industries: Meeting Agendas, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  December 7, 1933; January 4, 1934; February 1, 1934; February 15, 1934; March 22, 1934; July 24, 1934; August 28, 1934; November 1, 1934; February 7, 1935; March 8, 1935; March 14, 1935; May 8, 1935; May 13, 1935; May 15, 1935; May 16, 1935
- Code Authority Members Representative Capacity, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- "Code Chisel" (Collier's Article), 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Code of Fair Competition, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Code Requests, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Code Revisions Committee regarding Code Interpretations, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Collective Agreements (and Correspondence), 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Complaints to Code Authority (Fair Trade Practice), 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Compliance, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Designated Contractors (Regulations); Also: Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Enforcement Committee, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fact Finding Outline, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Fact Finding Commission Report: Boston, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  June 25, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission Report: Boston, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Fact Finding Commission: Chicago and Saint Louis, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  June 4, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: Reports: Cleveland, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  May 31, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: Kansas City, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  June 7, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: Los Angeles, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  June 11, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: New Jersey, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  June 26, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: New York, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  June 27, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: Philadelphia, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  June 22, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: Portland, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  June 15, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: San Francisco, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  June 13, 1934
- Fact Finding Commission: Seattle, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  June 16, 1934
- Fair Trade Practice (Decisions), 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Fair Trade Practice: Resolutions, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Fair Trade Practice Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Fur Label Committee regarding Label, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- General Council regarding John Keating, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Hearings and Investigations, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Hearings for Violations, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Industrial Council (Samuel Kline), 1933 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Imports and Foreign Commerce, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Industrial Council (Samuel Kline), 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Infants and Children Wear Code Authority, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Infants and Children Wear Code Authority Resolutions Regarding Article VI Appointment of Member to Code, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Insurance Records, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Intercode: National Recovery Board, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Investigation Reports, 1932-1933 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Investigations Request: Correspondence Alexander Printz, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Jobber-Contractor Relations (Committee), 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Joint Board Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Kansas City (Brand and Puritz) Offices Correspondence G.G. Shaw, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Label Companies: Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Labels: Correspondence, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  August-September 1933
- Labels: Correspondence, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  October 1933-1935
- Label regarding Jack Meyer Label Company, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Label Costs Resolutions regarding Baltimore Market (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Label regarding Counterfeit Label, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Label Publicity, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Label Stops, Label Decisions, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Labor Bureau Studies/Statistics, 1933-1935 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Labor Bureau Report, Fall Season, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Labor Bureau Report, Fall Season, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Labor Bureau Report, Spring Season, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Legal Council NRA Division, C.G. Raphael, 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Legal Fee, Harry Bergson (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Liquidation Damages for Code Violations, 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Local Number 35 Dress Pressers Union (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Los Angeles District, Julius Marcus (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Los Angeles, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Market Investigations Commission, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Men's Clothing Code Authority, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Merchant's Ladies Garment Association, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Millinery Code Authority (Max Meyer), 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- National Retail Code Authority, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- National Retail Dry Goods Association, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Non-Manufacturing Employees, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- NRA Orders, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Organization Committee Code Authority, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Overtime Requests and Petitions, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia Office Records (Samuel D. Bass), 1934 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  January-July 1934
- Philadelphia Office Records (Samuel D. Bass), 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  August-December 1934-1935
- "Piece Rate" Petitions regarding Independent Cloak Company, Incorporated, New Britain, Connecticut, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Portland Office Correspondence (Eugene Rosenberg, Carl Detering), 1935 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Rainwear Code Authority, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Records, Statements, and Orders, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Research and Planning Division: NRA, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Requests to Administration regarding Saturday working day in lieu of Jewish Holidays, 1933-1934 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- (Karrer) San Francisco Offices, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Security Deposits: with Commission of C and S Industry, 1932-1935 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  (1932, 1933) 1934, 1935
- Saint Louis Office (Sidney S. Cohen), 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Western Area Council, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Western Area Resolutions regarding wage scale (Abe Rosenberg), 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Wolf, F. Nathan: Personal Correspondence regarding conferences, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Wolf, F. Nathan: Personal Requests regarding pictures, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Work Stoppages, Strikes: Notifications, 1933-1935 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Activities and Operations of the National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  November 1, 1940-March 31, 1941
- Administrative Committee Meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  May-November 1939-1940
- Administrative Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Administrative Committee, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- The Apparel Industry: Reports, 1937-1941 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Budget and Financial Statements and Receipts, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Budget Committee, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Bulletins: to all members, 1935-1936 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  September 1935-June 1936
- Convention Pictures (Los Angeles), 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Correspondence: Nathan Wolf (to New York), 1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Dating Regulations, 1937-1941 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Delivery Charge Report, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Fair Trade Practice Bureau, Function of, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Infants' and Children's Coat Association Special Group, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Label Correspondence (regarding NRA returns), 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  January-June 1936
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  August 1937
- Semi-Annual Meeting: National Recovery Board, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  August 30-31, 1937
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  January 1938
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  June 1938
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  May 1939
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  December 1940
- Meeting: Administrative Committees, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  May 1941-December 1941
- Minutes of sixth Annual Meeting National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Meeting: Convention Reports (Box 4, Folder 17)
  May 1941
- Meetings of Committees, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Meetings of Committees, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Meetings of Committees, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Monthly Bulletins, 1939-1945 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  1939-1942; 1943-1945
- Publicity, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Research, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Resolutions, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Resolutions Adopted, Memorandum and Correspondence, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Resolutions Adopted, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  May 1945
- Ruling on Exchange, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Wolf: Correspondence, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Administrative Committee, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Administrative Committee, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Administrative Committee, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Administrative Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Budget Committee, 1946-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Dating Regulations Correspondence, 1937-1958 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Discount Matters Violations, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Labels, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  May 1946
- Meetings (committee), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  December 1947
- Meetings (Committee), 1947 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  January 1947
- Meetings (Committee), 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  January 1949
- Meetings (Committee), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  January 1950
- Meetings (Committee), 1951 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  January 1951
- Meetings (Committee), 1952 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  January 1952
- Meetings (Committee), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Meetings: National Executive Committee, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Meetings (Committee), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Meetings: National Executive Committee, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Meetings: National Executive Committee, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Meetings (Committee), 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Meetings: National Executive Board, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Meetings (Committee), 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Pacific Coast Region, 1947-1959 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Correspondence, 1946-1957 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Price Tags: Saks Fifth Avenue Violations, 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Public Relations Report, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Public Relations (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Resolutions, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Resolutions, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Resolutions, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Resolutions, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Resolutions, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Resolutions, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Resolutions, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Resolutions, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Resolutions, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Resolutions, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Resolutions, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Resolutions, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Ruling on Telephone and Telegram Charges, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Resolutions, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Resolutions, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Resolutions, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Administrative Committee Meetings, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  May 1963
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  October 1963
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  January 1965
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  October 1965
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  May 1966
- Administrative Committee Meeting, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  August 1967
- Administrative Committee Meetings, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  September 1969
- Amendments to Constitution and By-Laws (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Baltimore Office Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Baltimore Office Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Boston Region, 1957-1960 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Boston Office: General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Boston Office: General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Boston regional Office, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Samuel A. Weinrebe - Correspondence - Boston-New York, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Boston Office Correspondence, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- By-Laws, National Board, revised, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  May 10, 1961
- Revised By-Laws and Constitution, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Chicago Office and Market Letters, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Chicago Market: Label Status (Financial Purchase Record), 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Chicago Office General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Chicago Office General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Chicago Office General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Chicago Office General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Chicago Office General Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Cleveland Office (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Cleveland Office General Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Cleveland Office Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Dating Regulations Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Delivery Charges, F.O.B. Correspondence to, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Maps of New York City not filmed (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Discount matters, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Fair Trade Practices Suggested Revisions (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Executive Board, Members of National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry to, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Fashion Institute of Technology to, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Fashion Institute of Technology, 1963-1971 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Imports: Proposed Bill Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Imports: Research Materials, 1964-1971 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- International Lady Garment Workers Union, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Investigations and Violations to, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Labels Correspondence to, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Label Care, Textile Industry Committee, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles Office general Correspondence, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Los Angeles Office General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles Office General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Office General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Office General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles, Basil Feinberg, Legal Correspondence, 1964-1970 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles Market Correspondence, Maurice M. Grossman and Isidor Stenzar, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Meetings (Committee), 1961-1965 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Meeting: National Executive Board Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  February 1963
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Meeting: National Executive Board Reports, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Meeting: National Executive Board Correspondence, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Meeting: National Executive Board News Clippings and Publicity, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Proceedings 26th Annual Meeting of the National Executive Board of the National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  February 27, 1963
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Meeting: National Executive Board Reports, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  February 1964
- Meeting: National Executive Board Convention Correspondence, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Meeting: National Executive Board News Clippings and Publicity, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Proceedings 17th Annual Meeting of the Executive Board, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  February 24-26, 1964
- Meeting: National Executive Board Pictures, Publicity, correspondence, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  February-March 1966
- Meeting: National Executive Board - Reports, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  February-March, 1966
- Proceedings - 28th Annual Meeting - National Board of the Coat and Suit Industry, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Meetings (Committee), 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Meeting: National Executive Committee, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  December 1967
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Meetings (Committees), 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Meeting: Idea Collection Photos, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Meeting: News Clippings, etc., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Meeting: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Meeting: National Executive Board, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  February 1970
- National Board, Recovery Board, 1961-1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Pacific Coast Region Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Philadelphia Office - Market - Correspondence, 1961-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Philadelphia Office General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Philadelphia General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia Office General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Philadelphia Office General Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Philadelphia Office Market Open Items, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Philadelphia Office Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Regarding Pilferage, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Portland Office General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Portland Office General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Portland Office General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Portland Office General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Portland Office Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Public Relations Committee, Folder IV as of, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Public Relations: Factbook "Selling Fashion", 1962-1968 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Research Department, 1962-1966 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Resolutions, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Return Goods Policy: Revised regarding J.C. Penny Company, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- San Francisco Office General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- San Francisco Office General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- San Francisco Office General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- San Francisco Office General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- San Francisco Office Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Small Business Administration, New York City (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Saint Louis Office General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Saint Louis Office - Kansas City General Correspondence, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Saint Louis - Kansas City General Correspondence, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Saint Louis - Kansas City General Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Saint Louis - Kansas City Office Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Tariffs and Trades: Exports, General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade, 1961-1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Tariffs and Trade: Exports, General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Trucking/Traffic, National Textile Trucking Bureau, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Trucking, to, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Unemployment Insurance Taxes, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Union Label and Service Trade Department, 1964-1971 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Union Negotiations, Local 153, Agreements, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Union Negotiations, Local 153, Correspondence, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- 90-Day Wage-Price Freeze, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Zip Coats: Correspondence with Out of Town Markets, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Memorandum: Anti-Trust Laws (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Miscellaneous: Milton Levy, Nathan Wolf, 1940 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Constitution and By-Laws, 1940-1946 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Federal Trade Commission Correspondence, 1935-1938 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Federal Trade Commission regarding Stabilization, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Federal Trade Commission, St. Louis to, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 37)